Vikram Thangavel

22 Buttonwood Rd., Brampton ON, L6P 4J9 Phone: (647) 449-4025

Email: vikram1901shan@gmail.com

Objective

By integrating my academic skills and competencies acquired from my work experiences, I hope to be given a platform to display my skills and continuously improve them as I go. I would be a proficient asset to your company, as I will strive to exceed expectations, while offering fastidious and autonomous work.

Education

York University, Honours Bachelor of Computer Science

• Completed courses include: Programming in JavaScript and Android development, discrete mathematics in computer science, differential and applied calculus, and microeconomics

Secondary School Jeunes sans Frontières

High School Graduate (2015 – 2019)

Expected graduation: 2023

Work Experience

Burrito Boyz - Woodbridge, ON

July 2019 - Present

House Cook

- Assisting in the preparation of catering orders
- Developing knife and safety skills
- Preparing consistent and high-quality cuisine aligned with the restaurant's food preparation and handling standards

Canada's Wonderland - Vaughan, ON

July 2017 – January 2020

Supervisor

- Greeting customers and providing excellent customer service
- Handling money at the till and completing financial reports
- Assisting and training new staff members
- Cooking and serving food orders to customers
- Managing inventory by stocking and packaging the necessary materials
- Completing paperwork detailing all workload information

JetSki Ottawa – Ottawa, ON

May 2018 – August 2018

Part time developer

- Assisting in the development of a program in Java, which retrieves and displays geographic location of jet skis through text messages by using a SIM card for communication
- Cooperated with the owner of the company to ensure that the highest standards were met
- Provided in house testing of application

Skills acquired:

- Excellent customer service skills: managing inquiries about benefits, reservations, and events
- Planning and executing work with accuracy, in order of priority and deadlines
- Excellent inventory and project management skills
- Experience with software development through Java
- Adaptability from the ever-changing needs of the organization since it was a start-up

Certifications

Smart Serve Certification Food Handler Certification July 2018 August 2018

Skills and Competencies

- Fluent oral and written communication in both official languages (English and French)
- High proficiency in Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel, and Access
- Experience with Java, JavaScript and Android development
- Good interpersonal and communication skills
- Easily adaptable to new environments
- Good organization and time management skills

References available upon request